PRODUCTS = [
    {'name':'Baby Yoda Blueball', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Baby Yoda (Grogu) - The Mandalorian Saga, edici√≥n limitada.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':8, 'discount':5.00, 'sku':'STW001001', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp', 'image_back':'star-wars/baby-yoda-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':2, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Luke Skylwalker & Grogu', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Luke Skylwalker & Grogu - The Mandalorian Saga.', 'price':2399.99,'stock': 8, 'discount':15.00, 'sku':'STW001003', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'star-wars/luke-1.webp', 'image_back':'star-wars/luke-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':2, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Stormtrooper Lightsaber', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Stormtrooper Lightsaber - Star Wars Saga.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':8, 'discount':20.00, 'sku':'STW001004', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'star-wars/trooper-1.webp', 'image_back':'star-wars/trooper-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':2, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Charmander Smiley', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Charmander - Pokemon Saga.', 'price':1799.99,'stock': 8, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'PKM001001', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'pokemon/charmander-1.webp', 'image_back':'pokemon/charmander-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':1, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Dragonite Hi!', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Dragonite - Pokemon Saga.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':8, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'PKM001002', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'pokemon/dragonite-1.webp', 'image_back':'pokemon/dragonite-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':1, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Pidgeotto Flying', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Pidgeotto - Pokemon Saga.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':8, 'discount':30.00, 'sku':'PKM00103', 'dues':3, 'special':1, 'image_front':'pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp', 'image_back':'pokemon/pidgeotto-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':1, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Pikachu Smiley', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Pikachu - Pokemon Saga.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':8, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'PKM001004', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'pokemon/pikachu-1.webp', 'image_back':'pokemon/pikachu-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':1, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Vulpix Fancy', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Vulpix - Pokemon Saga.', 'price':99.99, 'stock':8, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'PKM001005', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'pokemon/vulpix-1.webp', 'image_back':'pokemon/vulpix-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':1, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Harry Potter & Hegwid', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Harry Potter & Hegwid - Harry Potter Saga.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':11, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'HPT001001', 'dues':9, 'special':0, 'image_front':'harry-potter/harry-1.webp', 'image_back':'harry-potter/harry-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':3, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Herminione Ball Dress', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Herminione - Harry Potter Saga.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':8, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'HPT001002', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'harry-potter/hermione-1.webp', 'image_back':'harry-potter/hermione-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':3, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Luna Lovegood Lion Mask', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Luna Lovegood - Harry Potter Saga.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':8, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'HPT001003', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'harry-potter/luna-1.webp', 'image_back':'harry-potter/luna-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':3, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Snape Patronus', 'description':'Figura coleccionable de Snape Patronus - Harry Potter Saga.', 'price':1799.99, 'stock':13, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'HPT001004', 'dues':3, 'special':0, 'image_front':'harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp', 'image_back':'harry-potter/snape-patronus-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':3, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Kakashi Hatake Shippuden', 'description':'Kakashi Hatake Shippuden', 'price':1999.99, 'stock':20, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'NRT001001', 'dues':9, 'special':0, 'image_front':'naruto/naruto-kakashi-1.webp', 'image_back':'naruto/naruto-kakashi-1-box.webp', 'licence_id':4, 'category_id':1},
    {'name':'Harry Potter', 'description':'Remera coleccionable de Harry Potter.', 'price':100.00, 'stock':999, 'discount':10.00, 'sku':'HPT003001', 'dues':6, 'special':1, 'image_front':'harry-potter/harry-3.webp', 'image_back':'harry-potter/harry-3-box.webp', 'licence_id':3, 'category_id':2}
]